Love by Chance is a romance, tv movie film directed by Gary Harvey.
Claire, an ambitious pastry chef, is busy running her new restaurant, but
her meddling mom is preoccupied with her lack of love life.
Without her knowledge, Claire’s mother finds her the perfect man, but when Claire finds out
it wasn’t fate that brought them together, it could ruin the relationship.
Claire Michaels, played by Beau Garrett.
Helen Michaels, played by Brenda Strong.
Eric Carlton, played by Benjamin Ayres.
Sam Michaels, played by Garwin Sanford.
Arnie Michaels, played by Peter Graham-Gaudreau.
Marco, played by John Cassini.
Cloudy with a Chance of Meatballs is a 2009 American animated science fiction comedy film written and directed by
Phil Lord and Christopher Miller, loosely based on the 1978 children's book by Judi and Ron Barrett.
It was produced by Columbia Pictures and Sony Pictures Animation, and stars the voices
of Bill Hader, Anna Faris, James Caan, Andy Samberg, Bruce Campbell, Mr.
T, Benjamin Bratt, and Neil Patrick Harris.
The film centers around an aspiring inventor named Flint Lockwood who develops, following a
series of failed experiments, a machine that can convert water into food.
After the machine becomes rogue and begins to develop food
storms, Flint must stop it in order to save the world.
Cloudy with a Chance of Meatballs premiered at the Mann Village Theater in Los Angeles on September 12,
2009, and was released in the United States on September 18 by Sony Pictures Releasing.
It was a box office success, grossing $243 million against a budget of $100M.
The film received positive reviews from critics and was nominated for
Best Animated Feature at the 67th Golden Globe Awards.
A sequel, Cloudy with a Chance of Meatballs 2, was released in 2013,
while an animated television series premiered in 2017.
The film explores themes of restaurant, romcom, matchmaking, chef.
The tone is emotional.